saudigulfairlines.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | SaudiGulf Airlines

## Sites covered by this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all SaudiGulf Airline owned websites and domains, and our wholly owned subsidiaries ("SaudiGulf Airline websites.")

## Types of information we collect

This Privacy Statement covers personal information and non-personal data collection and aggregate reporting.

a)“Personal information” is information that is associated with your name or personal identity. SaudiGulf Airline uses personal information to understand better your needs and interests and to provide you with better service. Once you choose to provide us with personal information, you can be assured it will be used only to support your customer relationship with SaudiGulf Airline. We take seriously the trust you place in us. SaudiGulf Airline will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others.

On some SaudiGulf Airline websites, you can order products or services, participate in surveys, request information, subscribe to marketing or support materials, register yourself or your SaudiGulf Airline products, or apply for a job or internship at SaudiGulf Airline or otherwise be required to provide personal information for other purposes. The types of personal information you provide to us on these pages may include name, address, phone number, e-mail address, user IDs and passwords, billing and transaction information, credit card information, contact preferences, educational and employment background, and job interest data. To personalize our websites, services or communications and improve our products and services, we may also ask you to provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, and experiences with our products or services. Providing this additional information is optional.

b)“Non-personal information” is data about usage and service operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. SaudiGulf Airline may collect and analyse non-personal information visitors’ domains to evaluate how visitors use the SaudiGulf Airline websites or otherwise analyze this data for trends and statistics purposes. Non-personal data we collect may include the pages visited on the SaudiGulf Airline websites, unique URLs visited within SaudiGulf Airline websites, browser type and IP address, but the individual visitor’s personal information remains anonymous.

Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. On most SaudiGulf Airline websites, we use cookies, web beacons and other technologies for data analysis and personalization services so that we can better serve you with customized information when you return to our site. We also use cookies and web beacons to help us measure the effectiveness of our web communication and marketing in order to improve our site, products, offers and marketing strategy.

SaudiGulf Airline also places ads on third party websites that may use cookies. We collect certain non-personal information about your browsing activity if you access the SaudiGulf Airline websites via an ad on a third party website. This information is used to analyze the performance of SaudiGulf Airline’s ad campaigns. We use the Google AdWords free conversion tracking feature for this purpose.

Cookies are identifiers which a website can send to your browser to keep on your computer to facilitate your next visit to the SaudiGulf Airline websites. To learn more, read SaudiGulf Airline use of cookies, web beacons and third party ads. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the option to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not wish to allow your session visitation information to be aggregated and analyzed by our web analytics service, you can opt-out in accordance with the procedure set forth in Section 9, “Your privacy preferences and opting out”.

## Collected information

We've structured the SaudiGulf Airline websites so that, in general, you can visit SaudiGulf Airline on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. We make this notice readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every SaudiGulf Airline web page.

There are times when we may collect personal information from you. It is our intent to inform you before we do that and to tell you what we intend to do with the information. Generally, you will have the option not to provide the information, and in the future you will be able to "opt out" of certain uses of the information. If you choose not to provide the information we request, you can still visit most of the SaudiGulf Airline websites, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers and services.
